[Music] It has
happened
[Music]
Hello friends, welcome to the Sanjya channel,
friends, in Position Talkies,
its name is Eid Gas
Chamber, so
friends, you have to book it on the current date, that is,
around 259, you have to like it
and friends, when you go around 19, you have to
wish it that
at 259, now you have to click on continue
and when it goes near 219, friends, then you
address it, now friends, here you have to
invest 50% of your capital, that is, 50% of your
capital will be invested
at 259
and the remaining 50% of your capital will be invested
at 219,
friends, the market is running on live time,
whenever you
get 10 to 15 percent in any stock, keep booking your profit,
whatever position stock it is, if
you have considered any toe for the long term, then
you should remain in it, whatever
dates are given below, you should go there and book the
office, whenever you withdraw money from your stock in the market,
friends, then you  If you have
pocket money
then never panic, you have to edit your position,
then friends, if you have
created your own portfolio of 10 or 12 stocks, then
what will be the maximum out of it,
friends, how will it be that Pizza,
suppose completely that
5 years ago, whichever bank you had
in your portfolio, you must have also
kept Chappell in your portfolio, and at one
time there were stocks like Satyam Computer Entertainment,
they also used to be in our portfolio,
but what happened, some of those
stocks definitely went down, but friends, it
means how much you have to be
100%, but
how much percentage you have to go up, there is
no count of it, 500%,
600, so you guys understand this thing,
if a single stock of yours goes up,
in the long term, that single stock of yours will be such that it will
even compensate for the loss of two-three stocks, so
if you are an investor for the long term, then you guys should stay
in your stock and good stock until you
get some big news sign that that stock has gone down, that is, the
company's  Some wrong
news starts coming in. A few days ago, one is made,
friends, sometimes you get a pack and
rumors spread, which are not like this in the company,
so first I would
not have opposed you, even a few days ago,
some water was created in U Bank,
in a single day the stock had broken 18 cents, so in
such a situation, you people and the note
website which is attacked with a knife, right now
you would have got a profit of 5% in intraday, so
you people have to think
in the market,
see the big meaning, you have to make a strategy,
people create panic and take small and get
scared in it and submit their position,
so you people should not get into Kabir panic, you have to
maintain your position,
friends, those who will take a position in this stock,
they have to take more than 250
and
in two, wish at 198, if it consolidates below 219 for
three-four days, then you will get attached to
your position,
so let's discuss the stock fundamentally,
it is difficult, come to Pappu, friends,
liquid, you can
Google  You can also search for it on this,
you can do this in both,
it is quite good
that if you talk about its financial end then
you will see that
its value has to be increased every year
and Afzal Hussain should decrease in the party
but it is covering 20 so fast
that if you
look at its huge profit then both are equal
and right now in 2012 the
company has six more months time and
if the company does well then you will get to
see very good results,
if you look at the pension statement in it then you will
see what a great stock it is, hey
Devendra, friends, if we talk about opposition then
where the revenue growth of the industry is
0.4 to 11.8 percent, the revenue growth of this company
is
22%, friends, the arrested accused is from the
color of the industry,
friends, the company has increased its market share from 6.5 to
11.1, almost doubling the company,
if we talk about less than the market then
where the net income of the industry is
31.6 to 1%, there the zone president of this company
Now you can see that the company is
getting support from the Amazon of the industry,
so you must be understanding this, so
friends, you must have liked this video and it will be
very beneficial for you, with this,
thank you
friends, if you like this video, then
please do not forget to like, share and subscribe,
thank you for watching my video
[Music]